(Howard(door bell rings):)That's Raj.
(Stuart:)You guys relax,
(Stuart:)I'll get it.
(Stuart:)Have some bread
while it's still warm.
(Howard:)It's like we have a butler.
(Howard:)If I had a Batsuit
I'd be Bruce Wayne.
(Bernadette:)You have a Batsuit.
(Howard:)It's pajamas, there's no cape.
(Stuart:)Hey, Raj.
(Raj:)Hey, Stuart.
(Raj:)What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm living here again.
(Raj:)Do, uh, Howard
and Bernadette know?
Or is it like a opossum
in the walls kind of thing?
(Stuart:)No, I needed a place to stay
(Stuart:)and, with the baby coming,
(Stuart:)I figured they could
use some extra help.
(Raj:)Okay, cool.
(Stuart:)Anyway, come on in,
dinner's ready.
(Raj:)Oh, but I bought
Chinese takeout.
(Stuart:)Oh, okay.
(Stuart:)Well, if Bernadette wants her
ankles to swell up even more,
(Stuart:)she can have that.
(Leonard:)Is the Wi-Fi working for you?
(Penny:)Uh, hang on.